Hey everyone, it's RaySist,
and I'm back with a
fully revamped version
of my blackmarket script,
RaySist-BlackmarketV2.
This isn't just an update,
it's a complete overhaul,
designed to give your FiveM
server the most flexible
and immersive underground
marketplace yet.
With the brand new modern NUI
interface, players can easily
browse and purchase weapons,
ammo, and black market
exclusives in a smooth
and interactive way.
Want full control?
You got it.
You can toggle qb-target, move
market locations, customize
prices, and even change
the items available,
all to fit your server's
economy and style.
No restrictions.
No unnecessary limitations.
Just a fully customizable
black market experience,
built for service.